http://www.radmin.com/privacy/

Privacy policy
Thank you for visiting Famatech’s website located at www.radmin.com. We are firmly committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. To that end, we are pleased to provide this Privacy Policy to describe our information gathering and use.
Acquisition of information
You may visit our site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Our site does collect information such as domain, IP address, browser type and operating system for site trends and statistics, but this information does not personally identify you.
We may ask you to provide personally identifiable information if you are signing up as our reseller and partner. Some information about your company, its size or other details may be required by us via email while providing pre-sale support.
We use an outside companies, element 5 and Regsoft, to ship orders and process credit cards. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
How we use the information
The personal information you provide will be used for the purpose for which it was provided - to contact you, to process an order, to register your product, etc. Famatech may also use any information you have provided as reasonably necessary to provide customer support to you. Famatech may also use your contact information to provide notices regarding the products or services that you have purchased, as well as to inform you about new products or promotional campaigns.
With whom we share your information
Famatech may share information with its billing companies Element 5 Inc. or Regsoft Inc. This is necessary for processing your orders or troubleshooting.
Your information may be shared with Famatech’s authorized resellers and partners who we may think would serve you better.
Information Security
Famatech will strictly protect the security of your personal information, protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Your personal data, including your e-mail address, is used for internal purposes only and is never sold or shared with anyone outside of Famatech or our authorized resellers, unless we disclose information in response to a law enforcement request.
Public Forums
Public forum is the part of the site. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information.
Any questions? Please contact us.
Copyright © 1999-2020 Famatech Corp. All rights reserved.
